

# **Dimpi jha**

**UI Developer** 

## **My Contact**

dimpijha92@gmail.com

**(**) 9576070485

0

Kolkata , West Bengal

#### **Career Objective**

Looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector.

#### **Hard Skill**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Jquery
- Javascript
- SASS
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- Illustrator
- Corel Draw
- Basic React js
- Basic Wordpress
- Illustrator
- Corel Draw
- Azure

#### **Education Background**

- Ranchi Womens College
  B.A Passed with Geography Hon. 55 %
- Kendriya Vidyalaya Dipatoli
  12TH Passed with 54 %
- xplora design skool
  One Year Diploma Course in (Web Design & Graphic Designer)

#### **About Me**

UI Developer with 5.5 years of experience designing and building responsive web design in the IT industry. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

### **Professional Experience**

# PWC (Third Party Payroll) | UI Devloper 2023

Key responsibilities:

- My current project is RBI, my work is on the frontend.
- I worked alone on the dark theme of RBI.
- Working with (stacks) and managing the front end team.
- Create reusable UI component to enhance devlopment efficiency
- and consistency across project.
- Currently Responsible for implement new design from XD.

## IGMI LEAD CONSULTANCY PVT LTD | Senior Web Designer 2021 - 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Responsible for creating all aspects of client websites, start to finish.
- Created an average of 6 minor websites or one major website per month.
- Design 200+ Websites for clients in a variety of industries.
- Build re-usable react components. Daily maintenance of code, debugging issues and solving clients' problems.
- projects on-time and with the highest standard, retaining over 98% of clients in a 3-year period.

## IGLOBAL IMPACT ITES PVT. LTD | Web Designer 2019 - 2021

- Key responsibilities:
- Has designed more than 100+ projects landing pages, Company websites and others.
- Completed projects an average of 90% before deadlines.
- Design Company website https://www.goigi.com/ and https://www.igiworld.net/ .

## Talent Technology Pvt. LTD | Web Designer 2018 - 2019

- Key responsibilities:
- Created custom graphics sets for clients, with 90% client satisfaction scores.
- Handled all composition, color, illustration, typography, and branding for client projects. Turned in projects an average of 5% faster than targets.